这蛋糕太好吃了
This cake is amazing!
天啊，去开房吧。
My God,get a room.
我会跟这个蛋糕去开房的
I would get a room with this cake.
正是时候让你们看看美味的蛋糕呢。
I think I could show this cake a good time.
如果你们必须放弃一样的话 你们会放弃哪一样儿，食物还是性爱？
If you had to,what would you give up,food or sex?
性爱
Sex.
说真的，你回答得也太快了吧
Seriously,answer faster.
不好意思，亲爱的
Oh,I'm sorry,honey.
我刚才说的性爱，并不是指和你一起的性爱
But when she said "sex," I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
好象我还受了很大恩惠似的。
It's like a giant hug.
罗斯，你呢？ 你会放弃哪一样？性爱还是食物？
Ross,how about you? Which would you give up?
食物
Food.
那如果是性爱和恐龙呢？
How about sex or dinosaurs?
老天啊，真是两难的选择啊。
Oh,my God,it's like Sophie's Choice.
哦，天啊
Oh,God.
乔，你放弃什么？性爱还是食物？
What about you,Joe? What would you give up,sex or food?
我不知道，这太难取舍了
I don't know,it's too hard.
不行，你必须得选一个
No,you gotta pick one.
食物，不，性爱
Food. No,sex.
食物，性爱，食物，性爱… 我不知道，老天，我都想要！
Food. Sex. Food. Sex.. I don't know! Oh,God,I want both!
我要坐在面包上的妞儿！
I want.. I want girls on bread!
钱德的外遇
The.One.With.Chandler.Gets.Caught
-我这儿有我女儿最新的照片 -哇，真可爱啊
- You gotta see these pictures of Emma. - Oh,how cute!
-她看上去就象个娃娃 -不不，那就是个娃娃
- She looks just like a little doll. - Oh,no,that is a doll.
噢，感谢上帝，因为我觉得它看上去有点吓人
Oh,thank God,because that thing's really creepy.
钱德在那儿
Look,there's Chandler.
噢，那个金发女郎是谁？她很漂亮
Who's the blond? She's pretty.
他有外遇了
He's having an affair.
他才不是有外遇呢
He is not having an affair!
你知道的啦，我在这事儿上面感觉很准的。
I'm always right about these things.
不，你才没有呢 上周你还在想罗斯想把你宰了
No,you're not. Last week,you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
对不起，但确实很让人难以相信
Well,sorry,but it's hard to believe that
有人能讲一个洋娃娃也会讲的故事。
anyone would tell a story that dull..just to tell it.
我敢发誓他们俩之间肯定有些什么事
There's something going on with them.
快看，他们俩上了同一部车
Look! He's getting into the car with her.
那并不能说明什么
That doesn't mean anything.
是吗？让我们走着瞧
Oh,yeah? Well,let's see.
喂,趴低点
Okay,duck down.
-喂? -嗨，钱德，我是菲比
- Hello? - Hi,Chandler. It's Phoebe.
我知道今天莫尼卡要上班
I know that Monica is working today..
所以我想你要不要跟我和瑞秋一起去看电影
so I was wondering if you wanted to come to the movies with me and Rachel.
噢，我也得上班。 我在这办公室里都闷了一天了
Oh,I have to work too. Yeah,I'm stuck here at the office all day.
太可惜了，你不能去看电影
Well,it's a shame that you'll miss the movie..
因为我们打算看《大话王》（1997年）
because we were gonna see,you know,either Liar Liar..
《危险女人心》（1983年）或者是《金玉盟》（1957年）
or Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
噢，这些片子可不是一般的老啊
Those are all really old.
是啊，也可能会看…
Okay,then maybe it'll be..
《猪头，我的车咧？》（2000年）
Dude,Where's My Car?
-什么？ -他们现在在车里
- What? - They're in a car.
好了，迟点再跟你说，再见
Okay. Well,talk to you later,okay? Bye.
快，我们得拦辆出租车跟踪他们
Okay,quick. We gotta find a cab and follow them.
好的，我得先去拿我的夜视镜和眩晕枪
Yeah,okay. Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
我这儿有
I got them.
-嘿 -嗨，亲爱的
- Hey. - Hey. Hi,sweetie.
你身上有香水和香烟的味道
Hey,you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
-我今天和南茜在车里面呆了一天 -南茜可不抽烟
- I was in the car with Nancy. - Nancy doesn't smoke.
那至少那香水不是我的 你这点到是不用担心。
Well,at least the perfume's not mine. Be thankful for that.
那么，你认为那房子怎么样？
So.. What did you think of the house?
简直太棒了，就是我们一直以来要找的
It's everything we've been looking for.
是吗？那些漂亮的涂层，冠形屋顶
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wanes coating..
偏厦窗子和阁楼？
the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
还有蠕虫和爬虫？
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps!
你刚刚在说什么？
What were the things you said?
-你喜欢那个大院子吗？ -还有睡房里的壁炉
- Don't you love the huge yard? - The fireplace in the bedroom.
南茜还说这个价钱非常优惠
And Nancy said it's really underpriced..
因为那家伙丢了工作不得不搬去跟父母住 所以急于出手。
because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents!
看把你兴奋的
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
你认为我们是不是应该把它买下来？
So do you think we should get it?
我不知道，你怎么想？
I don't know. What do you think?
-我想我们应该买下来 -我也这么想
- I think we should. - I do too.
这是件大事。 现在想不想抽一支？
This is huge. How bad do you wanna smoke right now?
你说什么呢，进言有功奖励香烟？
I don't know what you mean,giant,talking cigarette.
对了，我正在南茜车上的时候，菲比打电话来了
Phoebe called as I was getting into Nancy's car.
如果她问起就说我一天都在工作
If she asks you,I was at work all day.
明白，你打算什么时候跟他们说这件事
Got you. When do we tell them?
至少要等到事情完全确定下来，现在没有必要让大家都难受
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent. Why upset everybody over nothing?
嗯，好的
Okay. Right.
-上帝，这将会非常难受 -我知道。希望一切顺利
- Oh,my God,that is gonna be so hard. - I know. Good luck with it.
我只是不明白钱德为什么要骗莫尼卡
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
告诉你们吧，我们一直跟踪他们 到一所位于西切斯特的房子的外面
I'm telling you guys,we followed them out to a house in Westchester.
他们在里面待了有45分钟， 出来的时候两人看上去都很高兴
They went in for 45 minutes,and then they came out looking pretty happy.
钱德？
Chandler?
45分钟？
Forty-five minutes?
肯定有什么地方不对头
Well,something's not right.
所以你们跟踪到 西切斯特  还在外面等了45分钟
So you went all the way to Westchester,waited 45 minutes..
- 然后坐出租车回来？ - 是啊
- and came back in a cab? - Yeah.
如果你们谁愿意给100元的补助 那真是太好了
If each of you guys would like to pitch in 100 bucks,that would be great.
我不敢相信他这样对莫尼卡
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
是啊，而且他们就快有小孩儿了
I know,and with the baby coming?
-那我们该不该告诉莫尼卡？ -我不知道
- So should we tell her? - I don't know.
菲比，如果我们看到麦克跟另一个女人在一起，应不应该告诉你？
If one of us saw Mike with another woman,would you want us to tell you?
什么？你看到他跟谁在一起了？
Why? Who'd you see him with?
-没有，我只是说 -告诉我你知道些什么！
- No one. I'm just saying if we did.. - Tell me what you know!
我什么也不知道，我只是假设
No one! Nothing! Mike's a great guy! It was hypothetical!
好了，好了，他是个好人
All right. He is a good guy.
是啊，他是个好人，他不会骗我的
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
如果我真看到他跟另一个女人在一起…
If I did see him with someone,there's no way I..
你看见他跟谁在一起了？
Who did you see him with?
看，她多开心啊
Oh,look at her. So happy.
要是有更小的来清理这个该有多好
If only there were a smaller one to clean this one.
钱德在吗？
Hey,is Chandler here?
不在，他去买晚餐去了，出什么事了吗？
No,he's picking up dinner. Why? What's up?
无论发生什么事，我们都跟你在一起，我们爱你
Look,whatever happens,we're here for you,and we love you.
-好 -我想钱德可能有外遇了
- All right. - Chandler might be having an affair.
-什么？ -菲比和我今天
- What? - Phoebe and I saw Chandler..
看见钱德和一个金发女郎在一起
with a blond woman today outside on the street.
然后我们跟踪他们到了一所位于西切斯特的房子
And then we followed them to a house in Westchester.
他们一起进去了，很抱歉
They went in together. I'm so sorry.
我的上帝…太可怕了
Oh,my God. Oh,my God,that's awful.
你们觉得房子怎么样?
What did you think of the house?
什么？
What?
莫尼卡，你明白我们刚才说的话，对不对？
Monica,you understand what we're saying,right?
明白，当然明白 非常清楚你的意思
Yeah. Sure. I mean,I'm devastated,obviously.
你们认为那些邻居热不热情？
Did you think the neighborhood was homey?
- 嘿！ -你这个狗杂种
- Hey. - You son of a bitch.
你是在说我还是说附近不再受欢迎了？
Is it me,or have the greetings gone downhill around here?
菲比和瑞秋今天看见你和南茜在一起
Phoebe and Rachel saw you with Nancy today.
他们以为你和她有一腿
They think you're having an affair.
-谁是南茜？ -到底是怎么回事？
- Who's Nancy? - What's going on?
好的…
Okay..
好的，好的，伙计们，坐下说话
All right,you better sit down.
-这是件大事 - 是的
- This is.. This is pretty big. - Yeah.
我没有外遇
I'm not having an affair.
南茜是我们的房地产经纪
Nancy is our realtor.
我就知道他不可能跟一个女人做45分钟那么长
I knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes!
你们为什么要请地产经纪？
Why do you have a realtor?
最近以来她带着我们去看市区以外的房子
She's been showing us houses outside of the city.
-什么？ -你是说真的？
- What? - Are you serious?
我们认为因为我们马上就要有小孩儿了
When we found out that we were gonna get this baby..
我和钱德商量过了 我们决定不能在市区抚养我们的小孩儿
Chandler and I decided we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
所以你们要搬出去？
So you're.. So you're gonna move?
我的上帝！
Oh,my God.
这种事我们总要投票解决吧？
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
在市区里带小孩儿有什么不妥吗？
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
我不就正在市区里带小孩吗？ 罗斯也是
I'm doing it. Ross is doing it.
莎拉.杰西卡.派克也是这么干的
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it!
对你们来说这没什么问题 但是我们想要一个长长的秋千
And that's great for you guys,but we want a lawn and a swing set.
还有一条小孩可以在上面骑单车的马路
A street where our kids can ride their bikes..
不时还会有雪糕车经过
and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.
所以你们想买一栋50年代的房子？
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
你们有没有想过你们正放弃什么吗？
Have you thought about what you're giving up?
你们不能搬出市区
You can't move out of the city. What if..?
要是，要是你们想凌晨五点钟吃中餐怎么办？
What if you want Chinese food at 5 a.m.?
又或者想买一块一响就散架的假劳力士怎么办？
Or a fake Rolex that breaks as soon as it rains?
又或者是想召一个亚洲妓女怎么办？
Or an Asian hooker sent right to your door?
知道吗？如果你们只是想看看房子，没问题
You know what? If you want to look for a house,that's okay.
不，不， 不，别听他的 小心我扁你
No! No,it's not! Don't listen to him. I'm gonna thump you.
的确是没问题，等他们真正住进去之后
It's okay,because they have to get it out of their system.
你们会发现这里才是你们真正想要住的地方
Okay? But you're gonna realize this is the only place you want to be.
实际上
Actually..
我们已经找到合我们心意的房子了
we already found a house we love.
-什么？ -大约一小时以前，我们开出了我们的价码
- What? - About an hour ago,we made an offer.
我打赌你们现在宁可我有外遇
Bet you wish I was having an affair now,huh?
-你们已经开出价码了？ -那房子真的很好
- You put an offer on a house? - It's so sweet.
的确是，那里有一个很大的院子 一直通到一条小溪
It really is. It has this big yard that leads down to this stream.
那里还有很多枫树
And then there's these old maple trees.
跟自然环境有什么关系？你们又不是水獭
Oh,again with the nature. What are you,beavers?
我知道你们一时很难接受我们的决定， 我们也非常的抱歉
Look,I know this is really hard,and we're really sorry.
是不是因为我常不敲门就过来拿你们的东西吃?
Is this because I come over here without knocking and eat your food?
我可以不那样做
Because I can stop doing that.
我真的可以改
I really,really think I can.
乔,你知道这不是我们要搬出去住的原因
You know that's not the reason,Joe.
我想如果你们到实地看一看的话 你们会明白的
I think if you saw it,you'd understand.
你们俩去看过，那的确很美，不是吗？
You guys were there. It's beautiful,isn't it?
-是，确实是很美 -你在干什么？
- Yeah,it is. - What the hell are you doing?
我的意思是我们今天到那儿的时候 我所想的是
Well,it is,all right? When we were out there today,all I kept thinking was:
我简直不敢相信钱德在和那女人干那事儿，
"I can't believe Chandler's screwing this woman..
但那并不意味那里不是一个适合居住的地方！
but,man,this would be a nice place to live!"
是，但漂亮又能怎样？
Yeah,but so is this.
对，我是说如果你们搬到那里去住 你们就得离开这儿了
Yeah. I mean,if you move there,you have to leave here.
你们怎么能离开这个地方？
I mean,how can you leave this place?
爸爸，你听我说
Come on,Daddy,listen!
在我生命中 每个人总是对我说
All my life,everyone's always told me,"You're a shoe!"
你是鞋子！你是鞋子，你是鞋子！
"You're a shoe! You're a shoe. You're a shoe!"
今天我停下来说 如果我不想当鞋子会怎样？
I stopped and said,"What if I don't want to be a shoe?
如果我想做手袋？
What if I want to be a purse?
或是帽子？
Or a hat?"
不，我不是要你给我买顶帽子
I don't want you to buy me a hat,I..
我是说…我只是打个比方，爸爸！
It's a metaphor,Daddy!
你知道他的麻烦在哪里了
You can see where he'd have trouble.
好吧，也许我应该和莫尼卡待在这儿
Well,maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
我猜我们已经决定谁和莫尼卡住在一起了
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.
你的钱要归我啦，格林。
Your money's mine,Greene.
你的拉链没拉上，盖勒。
Your fly's open,Geller.
伙计们，知道我刚发现了什么吗？
You know what I just realized?
Joker（11）是带"J"的Poker（扑克牌）
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J"!
巧合吧？
Coincidence?
那真是带"C"的'巧合（joincidence）'
That's "joincidence" with a "C"!
呃，看，那个丑陋裸男点了一堆蜡烛
Look! Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
那一定很痛
That had to hurt!
嗨，这也是你们的感恩节
Hey,it's your Thanksgiving too.
除了看球赛，你也可以过来帮我们干点活
Instead of watching football,you could help.
我们会的
We know.
好了，瑞秋， 你想把这些软糖粒摆成一个同心圆
Rachel,you want to put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
不，莫尼卡， 是你想把它们摆成那样
No,Mon. You want to put them in concentric circles.
我只是想这样
I want to do this.
每年如此
Every year.
我被卡住了！
It's stuck!
小心阶梯
Step.
你怎么会把头给套进去了？
How did it get on?
我想把它戴上去吓吓钱德
I put it on to scare Chandler.
我的上帝，莫尼卡会抓狂的
Oh,my God! Monica's going to totally freak out!
还有，这里面难闻得要命
Plus,it smells really bad in here.
那是当然了 你脑袋伸到火鸡的屁股里面去了
Of course it smells bad. You have your head up a turkey's ass.
莫尼卡
Monica.
嗨，你们把火鸡……
Did you get the turkey..?
啊，我的上帝，我的上帝
Oh,my God!
这是什么？
Who is that?
是乔伊
It's Joey.
我明白了。
I got it!
如果我们赢，你们就得把那公鸡处理掉
If we win,they have to get rid of the rooster.
有意思？
That's interesting!
如果你们赢
If you win..
我们就放弃那只鸟儿
we give up the bird.
但是，如果我们赢了
But if we win..
我们要你们住的地方
we get your apartment.
- 一言为定！ -什么？
- Deal! - What?
莫妮卡当曲棍球守门员时候的绰号
"Monica's nickname when she was a hockey goalie?"
-大胖守门员 -正确。
- Big Fat Goalie. - Correct!
瑞秋说她最喜欢的电影是？
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
《危险关系》
Dangerous Liaisons.
-正确。实际上她最喜欢的电影是？ -《老板渡假去》
- "Her actual favorite movie is..?" - Weekend at Bernie's.
莫妮卡给她的毛巾分类， 一共分了多少类？
"Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?"
-每天用的 -正确
- Everyday use. - Fancy.
- 客人的 - 正确
- Guest. - Fancy guest.
- 2秒 - 11种？
- Two seconds. - Eleven?
太另人难以置信了，11是正确答案
Unbelievable! Eleven is correct.
钱德第一次摸女孩子胸部的时候有多大？
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
- 14? - 不,19.
- 14? - No,19.
谢了兄弟
Thanks,man.
乔伊有一个想象中的童年时的朋友
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
-他叫什么名字？ -莫里斯
- His name was..?" - Maurice!
-正确，他是干什么的？ -太空牛仔！
- "His profession was..?" - Space cowboy!
钱德是干什么工作的？
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
还有10秒，你们得答对这一题，否则就输了
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose.
嗯，好象是跟传送有关的
Something to do with transponding.
啊，啊，是搬运传送员！
He's a transponster!
你说的都不是一个正确的单词！
That's not even a word!
知道吗？你们是些卑鄙的家伙，太卑鄙了!
You are mean boys who are just being mean!
嗨，别冲我们发火！没人逼你越赌越大
Don't get mad! No one forced you to raise the stakes.
不对，是她逼我的！
That is not true! She forced me!
你答错题了。
You got the question wrong.
那是一个愚蠢的，不公平的问题。
It was a stupid,unfair question!
不要把责任怪在题上
Don't blame the questions!
你们能不能不要在屋子里瞎嚷嚷 你们把我们的搬家日给毁了
Stop yelling in our apartment! You are ruining moving day for us.
钱德！
Chandler!
钱德，我从窗户那里瞧见你们在干那事儿了
I saw what you were doing in the window!
我看见你在对我妹子做什么！ 现在你给我滚出去！
I saw what you're doing to my sister! Get out here!
哇！听着，我们在一起很快乐
Listen,we had a good run.
多久？ 四个月？五个月？
What was it? Four,five months?
这已经超过大多数人一辈子的恩爱时光了，所以再见，保重
That's more than most people have in a lifetime. Goodbye.
嘿，罗斯，出什么事了，老哥？
Hey,Ross. What's up,bro?
你们到底在干什么？！
What the hell are you doing?
嘿！出什么事了？
What's going on?
我想，我想罗斯知道我和莫尼卡的事了
I think Ross knows about me and Monica.
老兄,他就在那呢
Dude,he's right there.
我还当你是我最好的朋友呢！她可是我亲妹子。
I thought you were my best friend! This is my sister!
我最好的朋友跟我妹妹！我简直不敢相信！
My best friend and my sister! I cannot believe this!
我们不是玩玩而已的。 我爱她
We're not just messing around. I love her.
我跟她坠入情网了
I'm in love with her.
真不好意思，你是以这种方式知道我们相恋的
I'm so sorry that you had to find out this way.
抱歉，但这是真的，我也爱他
I'm sorry,but it's true. I love him too.
我最好的朋友和我妹妹！
My best friend and my sister!
我简直不敢相信！
I cannot believe this!
这是你最后一箱衣服
This is the last box of your clothes.
我想在这上面贴个标签：你在想什么？
I'm just gonna label it "What were you thinking?"
有趣，因为我正想到对门去 在钱德身上也写上这句话
I was gonna go across the hall and write that on Chandler.
二位，我不想把事情搞砸
Guys,I don't wanna make things worse,but..
但是，嗯，我再也不想跟瑞秋住在一起了
I don't want to live with Rachel anymore.
你们对对方太刻薄了！
You're so mean to each other.
而且我也不想跟瑞秋最后闹得不欢而散 我还是喜欢你
I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel. I still like you.
菲比，那没关系，因为我不搬了
That's fine because I'm not moving.
哇，哇，哇，菲比，你得跟她一起住！
Phoebe,you gotta take her.
你知道，我是曾说过一些她的坏话
I said some bad stuff..
但是，瑞秋还是有很多优点的， 这足以让她成为一个好的室友
but Rachel has qualities that make her a good roommate.
她有很多商品目录，嗯 她会把那些她认为我会喜欢的产品所在页折起来
She gets tons of catalogs and folds down the pages of things I'd like.
还有呢？
What else?
我在洗澡的时候
When I take a shower..
她会在镜子上给我留下留言
she leaves me notes on the mirror.
是，那是我干的
I do. I do do that.
很好，我喜欢在洗手间里读点东西
That's nice. I like having things to read in the bathroom.
当我看完书在沙发上睡着的时候，
When I fall asleep on the couch..
她会为我盖上一张毯子
she covers me with a blanket.
你知道啦，我不想让你着凉了
Well,you know,I don't want you to be cold.
还有，当我告诉她 我要跟钱德一起住的时候，
And when I told her that I was gonna move in with Chandler..
她真的是很支持我
she was really supportive.
你太好了
You were so great.
你把一件困难的事情变得轻松简单
You made it so easy.
现在，你得走了
And now you have to leave.
而我得和男生住在一起！
And I have to live with a boy!
-她真的走了 -我知道
- She really left. - I know.
-谢谢 -没问题，室友
- Thank you. - No problem,roomie.
-我能问你一个问题吗？ -当然！
- Can I ask you a question? - Sure.
那只狗倒底在那儿干什么？
What the hell is that dog doing here?
我来说点祝酒词吧
A little toast here. Ding,ding!
我知道这并不是你们所计划的感恩节
This isn't exactly the kind of Thanksgiving you planned..
但对于我来说，这个节真的是太棒了
but for me this has been really great.
知道吗？我之所以这样认为是因为 这个节里面没有离婚和
I think because it didn't involve divorce..
吐得一塌糊涂
or projectile vomiting.
无论怎样，我只是在想，如果你去了山谷
If you had gone to Vail..
如果你和你的家人在一起
or if you had been with your family,or if you didn't have..
如果你没做性病这类的广告
syphilis and stuff..
我们就不可能在一起，对不对？
we wouldn't be all together.
所以，我想说的是
So I guess what I'm trying to say is..
我很感激你们 因为你们的感恩节计划全砸了
that I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
-太感人了 -谢啦
- That's so sweet! - Thank you.
为糟糕的圣诞节干杯
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
也为糟糕的新年干杯
And a crappy New Year!
- 干杯！ -干杯！
- Hear,hear! - Hear,hear!
你们不能搬，你们就是不能这样做
You can't move. You just.. You just can't.
瑞秋说得对，你们俩是属于这里的
Rachel's right. This is where you guys belong.
是啊，你们可不能搬到西切斯特，那是最糟糕的切斯特。
You don't wanna live in Westchester. That's the worst of the Chesters.
知道吗，有时我独自一人在我的寓所的时候 望向这边
You know,sometimes when I'm alone in my apartment,I look over here..
你们正在吃晚餐
and you guys are just having dinner..
看电视或是做着其它什么事
or watching TV or something..
这让我感觉好很多
but it makes me feel better.
现在，你们搬走之后 我再望过来的时候，我会看到谁？
And now when I look over,who am I gonna see?
高特里？杨？
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
他们不会让我感觉如此之好！
They don't make me feel so good.
是啊，所以别搬了 对，就留下吧
Yeah. So don't move,okay? Just stay here..
-晚上的时候别忘了拉窗帘就行了。 - 喂！
- and maybe close your blinds at night. - Hey.
喂?
Hello?
是南茜，他们答复我们开出的价码了
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
然后？
And?
好的，谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
他们否决了
They passed.
他们不想对价格做任何让步
They said they won't go a penny under the asking price.
-我们负担不起那价格 -我知道
- We can't afford that. - I know.
好了，如你们所愿了
Well,there you go.
真抱歉
I'm really sorry,you guys.
我也很抱歉。要是那个电话
Yeah,I'm sorry too. I'm even more sorry that phone call didn't come..
在我说出从 窗户那边望过来之前打来的话，就好了。
before I told you about looking through the window.
我们还是让你们俩单独待一会儿吧
Yeah. Well,we're gonna let you be alone.
-你们没事吧？ -我们没事的
- You gonna be okay? - Yeah,we'll be okay.
我爱你们
Love you guys.
很抱歉，刚才没有支持你们
You know,I'm really sorry I wasn't more supportive before.
没关系，我们能理解
That's okay. We understand.
对了，关于这个南茜
Yeah,and about this Nancy..
如果你没跟她上床的话，能不能让我上？
If you're not sleeping with her,should I?
我知道外面还有很多房子，但是这栋…
I know there'll be other houses,but I just..
-我太爱这栋房子了 - 是啊
- I love that one so much. - Yeah.
所以得到这栋房子是天大的喜事
Well,it's a good thing we got it then.
-什么？ -我们买到那房子了
- What? - We got the house.
-噢，我的上帝 -我只是不想当着他们的面告诉你
- Oh,my God. - I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
我的上帝，上帝啊，我们买到那栋房子了
We got it?! We got the house?!
我们买到那栋房子了
We're getting a house!
-对，我们买到了 -还有孩子
- We're getting a house. - And a baby.
我们长大了
We're growing up.
是啊。
We sure are.
-谁去跟他们说呢？ -不是我
- Who's gonna tell them? - Not it!
也不是我，晚了一步
Not it! Damn it!
瑞秋，这是给你的
Rachel,this is yours.
为什么送我们这些礼物？
Why? What are these for?
-过会就知道了 - 好了，大家都请打开来看看吧
- You'll see. - All right,everybody open them.
好漂亮啊
Wow,this is so beautiful!
这个正是我上次在商店里相中的那一款小饰品！
These are the ones I was looking at in the store!
-我知道 -我喜欢这个
- I know. - Oh,I love this!
赛百味肉球三明治！
A meatball sub!
谢谢
Thanks!
说真的，你们怎么了？ 为什么送我们这些礼物？
Seriously,guys,what's going on? What are these for?
我先前不知道该怎么跟你们说
Well,I didn't know how to tell you before..
-但是，我们买到那房子了 -好好享受吧
- but we got the house. - Enjoy!
他们刚才说什么？
What did they say?